

→ DETAILS →

3 Street La Goulette Borj El Baccouche Ariana, Tunis, 2080,

Tunisia

+21629300943

imene.jalel@gmail.com

DATE OF BIRTH

31/08/1994

NATIONALITY

Tunisian

DRIVING LICENSE

car driving licence (category B)

LINKS -

LinkedIn

LANGUAGES

Arabic

French (DELF B2 PRO:92.5/100)

English (Toeic: 900/990)

SKILLS •

Lean Manufacturing

Project management

CMMS module in SAGE EM

Manufacturing module in SAGE EM

Inventory management module in SAGE EM

Logistics Management (Warehouse Management, Demand Planning, Materials Planning)

C#

L4G

SolidWorks: Level A Certificate

IMENE JALEL

Industrial and Logistics Systems Engineer

PROFILE

Industrial and Logistics Systems Engineer with experience in ERP consulting and supply chain optimization in multiple multinational industries (automotive, aircraft and food industries).

I have a true passion for manufacturing systems optimization and supply chain management.

■ EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Technical-functional consultant SAGE EM at Discovery Informatique, Tunis August 2018 — Present

Managing projects from customer needs definition to developing creative and specific solutions.

INTERNSHIPS

Final project internship at Zodiac Aerospace, Tunis

February 2018 — July 2019

Optimization of the internal logistic flows from the reception of the raw material to the production system.

ENGINEERING INTERNSHIP at Valeo, Tunis

June 2018 — July 2018

Muda Hunting and implementation of the 5S workplace organization method.

ENGINEERING INTERNSHIP at SOTUCHOC, Tunis

June 2017 — July 2017

Mapping SOTUCHOC's Supply Chain (VSM)

EDUCATION

Engineering degree in Industrial and Logistics Systems Engineering, National Engineering School of Carthage, Tunis

September 2019 — July 2018

Engineering Preparatory Classes Mathematics-Physics, Preparatory Institute for Engineering Studies of Tunis (IPEIT), Tunis

September 2019 — June 2015

EXTRA- CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

General Secretary at Hayyou'Raqs Association, Tunis

January 2018 — December 2019

The Association's goal is to support and promote the Art of Choreography.

Web redactor at AS DU WEB, Teleworking

September 2019 — February 2018

Writing web content for several French sites

Classical dance teacher for beginners, Tunis

July 2014 — August 2016